Guide to the Records of American Association for Ethiopian Jews (AAEJ), undated, 1960-1961, 1963, 1965-1968, 1970-1995, 2001-2002 *I-503
American Jewish Historical Society, Boston, MA and New York, NY
- Subgroup VI: Oversized Materials, undated, 1981-1988, 1990-1991; 1 oversized OS1 box, OS6F Folder 1.
  - OS1F Folder 2, undated, 1983-1986, 1988 (Box OS1F, Folder 2)
    2. Scale Plan of the Landscaping and Playground for Chamah School in Kiryat Malachi, Israel, undated (separated from Box 94, Folder 8)
    3. "Our Kind of Federation - Some of the whos, whats and wheres of Chicago's Jewish Federation," undated (separated from Box 94, Folder 18)
    4. CSAE Forum, December 1983, January 1984 (separated from Box 95, Folder 1)
    5. "The Jews of Ethiopia: People in Transition," The Forward, November 28, 1986 (separated from Box 101, Folder 17)
    6. Chicago Coalition for Ethiopia Invitation to a Stay Home Dinner for Ethiopia, June 12, 1988 (separated from Box 103, Folder 12)
    7. Famine articles, Washington Post, June 26-27, 1983 (separated from Box 104, Folder 10)
    8. Film Advertisement for "Falasha: Exile of the Black Jews of Ethiopia," March 1985 (separated from Box 105, Folder 1)
    9. Film Poster: "Falasha: Exile of the Black Jews," undated (2 copies) (separated from Box 105, Folder 2)
    10. Film Advertisement for "Falasha: Exile of the Black Jews," B'nai Brith Messenger, April 6, 1984 (separated from Box 105, Folder 3)
    11. Film Advertisement for "Falasha: Exile of the Black Jews," Israel Today, April 6, 1984 (separated from Box 105, Folder 3)
    12. Film Advertisement for "Falasha: Exile of the Black Jews," Israel Today, April 9-10, 1984 (separated from Box 105, Folder 3)
  - OS1F Folder 3, undated, 1982-1988 (Box OS1F, Folder 3)
    1. RPC Voice, Spring 1988 (separated from Box 106, Folder 21)
    2. Network Spectrum, December 1983 (separated from Box 106, Folder 27)
    3. Jewish Students of America, Winter 1987 (separated from Box 106, Folder 27)
    4. Noah's Ark, April 1985 (separated from Box 107, Folder 8)
    5. Special Ethiopian Jewry Free Book Offers, undated (separated from Box 107, Folder 11)
    6. Contemporary Publications, Spring 1982, Summer 1982 (separated from Box 107, Folder 24)
    7. Original Ads, 1982-1983 (separated from Box 107, Folder 26)
    8. Two Passover Broadsides from Northern California Jewish Bulletin, April 13, 1984 (separated from Box 108, Folder 7)
    9. "A Personal Passover: A Guide to Building Your Own Seder," Women's World, February/March 1988 (separated from Box 108, Folder 7)
    10. RPC Voice, Spring 1985, Summer 1985, October 1985, Winter 1985/86, Summer 1986, Spring 1987, and Special Edition (separated from Box 108, Folder 11)
  - OS1F Folder 4, undated, 1982-1986, 1988, 1991 (Box OS1F, Folder 4)
    1. "The Falashas: The black Jews in Ethiopia - a pictorial essay," The Jewish Week, July 15, 1983 (separated from Box 108, Folder 16)
    2. The Grantsmanship Center Whole Nonprofit Catalog, Winter 1984/1985 (separated from Box 109, Folder 31)
    3. Refugees, December 1983 (separated from Box 111, Folder 4)
    4. "Christians in Solidarity with Israel," reprint from New York Times, August 1, 1982 (separated from Box 112, Folder 8)
    5. Shofar, publication of the Sacramento Jewish Federation, October 1988, November 1988, December 1988 (separated from Box 113, Folder 8)
    6. "Sudan Tries General Who Saved Falashas," JINSA Security Affairs, February 1986 (separated from Box 116, Folder 10)
    7. "Our heroes of Sudan," Toronto Star, August 4, 1984 (separated from Box 116, Folder 26)
    8. "Operation: Teffilin" Advertisement, Jewish Press, April 4, 1986 (separated from Box 117, Folder 7)
    9. "Nisht Geferlack Klezmer Band" in concert, a benefit for Falasha Jews of Ethiopia, October 20, 1984 (separated from Box 118, Folder 31)
    10. Poster: "Falasha: Exile of the Black Jews," Hyatt Regency Hotel, Atlanta, GA, undated (separated from Box 150, Folder 9)
    11. Poster: "Second Annual Lobby for the Release of Ethiopian Jews," Student Action for Ethiopian Jews, April 9-10, 1991 (2 copies) (separated from Box 171, Folder 16)
  - OS6F Folder 1, undated, 1981, 1983-1987, 1990-1991 (Box OS6F, Folder 1)
    1. Poster: "These People Are Devout Jews…," undated (5 copies) (separated from Box 4, Folder 12)
    View poster
    2. Poster: "If Not Now, When?", 1987 (in Yiddish) (separated from Box 11, Folder 16)
    3. "Ethiopia: Famine and flight," The Boston Globe, December 3, 1984 (separated from Box 14, Folder 1)
    4. Poster: "10th Annual CAJE Conference on Alternatives in Jewish Education," 1985 (separated from Box 95, Folder 26)
    5. Cushman Agency advertisement, Chicago Tribune, June 27, 1983 (separated from Box 101, Folder 4)
    6. Book Cover: "Falasha No More: An Ethiopian Jewish Child Comes Home," by Arlene Kushner, 1986 (separated from Box 104, Folder 8)
    7. Poster: "Save Persecuted Jewry!," World Union of Jewish Students, 1981 (separated from Box 109, Folder 17)
    8. Poster: "Ethiopian Artists Working in Clay," October 1987 (separated from Box 109, Folder 18)
    9. "Airlift to Israel," World Newsmap, February 11, 1985 (separated from Box 119, Folder 25)
    10. "Trapped in the Housing Maze," The Jerusalem Post, September 18, 1987 (separated from Box 168, Folder 8)
    11. Poster: "Lobby for the Release of Ethiopian Jews," March 27-28, 1990 (4 copies) (separated from Box 171, Folder 15)
    12. Poster: "Lobby for the Release of Ethiopian Jews," April 9-10, 1991 (separated from Box 171, Folder 15)